Contact

815-666-4903 (Mobile) i.83.waddell@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ianwaddell2000 (LinkedIn) github.com/IWaddell01 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Django
React.js

Certifications

Front-End Software Engineering Full Stack Software Engineering

Honors-Awards
Illinois State Scholar

Ian Waddell

Full Stack Engineer - React | JavaScript | Python | Django Crest Hill

Summary

I'm an aspiring software engineer and serious computer hardware enthusiast. Strong analytical and troubleshooting skills thanks to a decade of tinkering with anything and everything, experienced in full stack development including but not limited to Javascript, React, Python, Django, and RES

Experience

DoorDash Doordash September 2019 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Kenzie Academy Software QA Tester(Student Project) April 2021 - April 2021 (1 month)

I was the main QA Tester in my group capstone project at Kenzie Academy developing a Dropbox style website from scratch using the Django framework. In addition to contributing to the code, my main duties were insuring there was no bugs, handling Github pull requests and any merge conflicts, and insuring the project was ready for presentation.

Education

Kenzie Academy

Certification, Full-Stack Web Development · (2020 - 2021)

Lockport Township High School

· (2014 - 2018)